https://www.adaptermart.com/privacy-notice-ezp-9.htm

Home /
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
AdapterMart respects your privacy. Across our business, around the world, we will only collect, store and use your personal information for defined purposes. We use your information to support and enhance our relationship with you, for example, to process your purchase, provide service and support, and share product, service and company news and offerings with you. We do not sell your personal information. We only share your personal data outside the AdapterMart family of companies with your consent, as required by law or to protect AdapterMart, its customers, or the public, or with companies that help AdapterMart fulfill its obligations with you, and then only with partners who share AdapterMart's commitment to protecting your privacy and data. At any time you may contact AdapterMart with any privacy questions or concerns you may have. You also may ask at any time to see the personal data you have given us and request correction or deletion. We strive to protect the security of your personal data by use of appropriate measures and processes.
Privacy and Data Security
At AdapterMart, your right to privacy and data security is a primary concern. That's why, when you visit AdapterMart.com, we help you maintain control over your personal data on the Internet. Below are the guidelines we use for protecting the information you provide us during a visit to our Internet site or when you use our online support offerings such as contact_us.html.
AdapterMart only asks for specific types of personal information
In a few areas on our Web site and online customer support tools, we ask you to provide information that will enable us to enhance your site visit, to assist you with purchase and technical support issues or to follow up with you after your visit. It is completely optional for you to participate.
For example, we request information from you when you:
Register on AdapterMart.com
Request a quote
Place an order
Provide feedback in an online survey
Request e-mail notification of your order status
Subscribe to a newsletter or a mailing list
Request assistance from our "Live Help Desk!"
Fill out a support request
Information we may request includes your name, e-mail address, phone number, address, company name, credit card details, customer preference information, customer number and order number, as well as other similar personal information. If we ever ask for significantly different information we will inform you.
AdapterMart only uses your personal information for specific purposes
The information you provide will be kept confidential and used to support your customer relationship with AdapterMart. Among other things, we want to help you quickly find information on laptopbatterysell.com and alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new products and services from AdapterMart. Agents or contractors of AdapterMart who have access to your personal information and prospect information are required to keep the information confidential and not use it for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for AdapterMart. AdapterMart may enhance or merge your information collected at its site with data from third parties for purposes of marketing products or services to you.
In addition, AdapterMart may be required to disclose personal information in connection with law enforcement, fraud prevention, regulation, and other legal action or if AdapterMart reasonably believes it is necessary to do so to protect AdapterMart, its customers, or the public.
AdapterMart will not disclose your personal information to any outside organization for its use in marketing without your consent
Information regarding you (such as name, address and phone number) or your order and the products you purchase will not be given or sold to any outside organization for its use in marketing or solicitation without your consent. Your information may be shared with agents or contractors of AdapterMart for the purpose of performing services for AdapterMart.
Internet Commerce
The online store at laptopbatterysell.com is designed to give you options concerning the privacy of your credit card information, name, address, e-mail and any other information you provide us. AdapterMart is committed to data security with respect to information collected on our site. We offer the industry standard security measures available through your browser called SSL encryption, at our payment gateways. It has always been a AdapterMart practice to contact customers in the event of a potential problem with your purchase or any normal business communication regarding your purchase.
You can opt-out of AdapterMart's marketing list at any time
Periodically, we may send you information about our various products and services, or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you. Only AdapterMart (or agents working on behalf of AdapterMart and under confidentiality agreements) will send you these direct mailings. If you do not want to be included on AdapterMart's marketing list, simply tell us when you give us your personal information. Or, at any time you can easily opt-out of AdapterMart's marketing list or update your information by logging in your personal account.
Customized Experience
We use technology to help us deliver customized visitor experiences. At AdapterMart, we primarily use "cookies" to help us determine which service and support information is appropriate to your machine and to maintain your shopping experience in our online store. Our use of this technology does not mean that we automatically know any information about you. We might be able to ascertain what type of computer you are using, but beyond that, our use of cookies is designed only to provide you with a better experience when using www.laptopbatterysell.com. AdapterMart has no desire or intent to infringe on your privacy while using the laptopbatterysell.com site.
Third-Party Sites
Please be aware that other web sites that may be accessed through our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those third-party web sites linked to laptopbatterysell.com are not covered by this privacy statement.
You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. While we strive to protect your personal information, AdapterMart cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.
Other Web sites
AdapterMart's Web site contains links to other Web sites that are not operated by AdapterMart. AdapterMart is not responsible for the privacy practices of the Web sites that it does not operate. Some parts of the Web site are animated using various downloadable applications, such as Macromedia's Shockwave/Flash. Futures-Careers, Macromedia operate under their own privacy and security policies, and the way they may collect
Contact AdapterMart
If you would like to contact us for any reason regarding our privacy practices, please write us at the following email address:
laptopbatterysell@gmail.com
You may also click here and fill out the e-mail form under the topic: "Privacy Info: Request"
AdapterMart wants to help you keep your personal information accurate
To view or edit the information that has been stored online, please visit the My Account of the AdapterMart Web site.
Changes to the Policy
We reserve the right to change the terms, conditions, notices and ploicy under which this website is offered without notice at any time.
